const sampleData = [
  {
    date: "2023-01-01",
    question: "What special day is celebrated on January 1, 2023?",
    answer: "New Year's Day",
  },
  {
    date: "2023-02-14",
    question: "What holiday is on February 14, 2023?",
    answer: "Valentine's Day",
  },
  {
    date: "2023-03-17",
    question: "Which event is celebrated on March 17, 2023?",
    answer: "Saint Patrick's Day",
  },
  {
    date: "2023-04-01",
    question: "What is the significance of April 1, 2023?",
    answer: "April Fool's Day",
  },
  {
    date: "2023-05-01",
    question: "What is the international event observed on May 1, 2023?",
    answer: "International Labor Day",
  },
  {
    date: "2023-01-01",
    question: "What special day is celebrated on January 1, 2023?",
    answer: "New Year's Day",
  },
  {
    date: "2023-02-14",
    question: "What holiday is on February 14, 2023?",
    answer: "Valentine's Day",
  },
  {
    date: "2023-03-17",
    question: "Which event is celebrated on March 17, 2023?",
    answer: "Saint Patrick's Day",
  },
  {
    date: "2023-04-01",
    question: "What is the significance of April 1, 2023?",
    answer: "April Fool's Day",
  },
  {
    date: "2023-05-01",
    question: "What is the international event observed on May 1, 2023?",
    answer: "International Labor Day",
  },
  {
    date: "2023-06-21",
    question: "What occurs on June 21, 2023, in the Northern Hemisphere?",
    answer: "Summer Solstice",
  },
  {
    date: "2023-07-04",
    question: "What important day is celebrated in the USA on July 4, 2023?",
    answer: "Independence Day",
  },
  {
    date: "2023-08-15",
    question:
      "Which significant national holiday occurs in India on August 15, 2023?",
    answer: "Independence Day",
  },
  {
    date: "2023-09-10",
    question: "What special event is observed on September 10, 2023?",
    answer: "World Suicide Prevention Day",
  },
  {
    date: "2023-10-31",
    question: "What festival is widely celebrated on October 31, 2023?",
    answer: "Halloween",
  },
];

export default sampleData;
